
[
{
	"front": "George...was the first preseient of the United States."
	"back": "George Washington"
},
{
	"front": "John...was the second preseient of the United States."
	"back": "John <Adam></Adam>s"
},
{
	"front": "Thomas...was the third preseient of the United States."
	"back": "Thomas Jefferson"
},
{
	"front": "James...was the fourth preseient of the United States."
	"back": "James Madison"
},
{
	"front": "James...was the fifth preseient of the United States."
	"back": "James Monroe"
},
{
	"front": "John...was the sixth preseient of the United States."
	"back": "John Quincy Adams"
},
{
	"front": "Andrew...was the seventh preseient of the United States."
	"back": "Andrew Jackson"
},
{
	"front": "Martin...was the eigth preseient of the United States."
	"back": "Martin Van Buren"
},
{
	"front": "William...was the nineth preseient of the United States."
	"back": "William Henry Harrison"
},
{
	"front": "John...was the tenth preseient of the United States."
	"back": "John Tyler"
},
{
	"front": "James...was the eleventh preseient of the United States."
	"back": "James K. Polk"
},
{
	"front": "Zachory...was the twelfth preseient of the United States."
	"back": "Zachory Taylor"
},
{
	"front": "Millard...was the thirteeth preseient of the United States."
	"back": "Millard Fillmore"
},
{
	"front": "Franklin...was the fourteenth preseient of the United States."
	"back": "Franklin Pierce"
},
{
	"front": "James...was the fifteenth preseient of the United States."
	"back": "James Buchcanan"
},
{
	"front": "Abraham...was the sixteenth preseient of the United States."
	"back": "Abraham Lincoln"
},
{
	"front": "Andrew...was the seventh preseient of the United States."
	"back": "Andrew Johnson"
},
{
	"front": "Ulysses...was the eighteenth preseient of the United States."
	"back": "Ulysses S. Grant"
},
{
	"front": "Rutherford...was the nineteenth preseient of the United States."
	"back": "Rutherford B Hayes"
},
{
	"front": "James...was the twentieth preseient of the United States."
	"back": "James A. Garfield"
},
{
	"front": "Chester...was the twenty first preseient of the United States."
	"back": "Chester Arthur"
},
{
	"front": "Grover...was the twenty second preseient of the United States."
	"back": "Grover Cleveland"
}]
